It's probably somewhere around that.
その辺にあるんだよね、多分
It's my first time coming here too, so I don't know.
俺も初めて来るからさ、分かんないんだけど
Probably around that.
多分その辺
perhaps?
多分?
Wait a minute.
ちょっと待ってね
reception.
受付
Is it here?
ここかな?
Oh, here it is.
あ、ここだここだ
I have to accept this once.
ここ一回受付しなきゃいけないから
Wow that's amazing.
わーすごー
amazing.
すごい
Oh, there are so many.
え、めっちゃあるじゃん
Amazing.
すごー
Wow that's amazing.
わーすごー
There are so many.
めちゃくちゃあるね
Surprised.
びっくり
I didn't understand this feeling.
こんな感じわかってなかった
Oh, wait.
え、待って
Wait, wait.
待って待って
Rin-chan, look, look, look.
リンちゃん見て見て見て
Aren't these mushrooms amazing?
このキノコすごくない?
Wait, what is this?
なんか、これ何?
Ghibli?
ジブリ?
Doesn't it look like Ghibli anymore?
なんかもうジブリっぽくない?
surely.
確かに
Looks like something from Narusika.
ナルシカとかに出てきそう
I eat big food.
私、おっきいの食べるの
Is it big?
おっきい?
Yes, I want to eat something big.
うん、おっきいの食べたい
Is it big?
おっきいの?
Ah, Micchan, this.
あ、みっちゃん、これ
It's true.
本当だー
Isn't this big?
これ、おっきくない?
Okay, Bucko.
いいよ、バッコ
I'll take it.
俺、持ってあげる
thank you.
ありがとう
Huh, is this the root?
え、これ、根元かな?
I said cut it off from the root.
俺、根元から切ってって言ってたよ
Can it be cut?
切れる?
difficult.
難しい
difficult?
難しい?
Eh, not at all.
え、全然ちょっと
Wait a minute, that's difficult.
ちょっと待って、難しい
Isn't it possible?
できるんじゃない?
Oh, it's broken, this one is better.
あれ、割れちゃった、こっちの方が
What, a lie?
え、嘘?
Eh, but isn't it hard?
え、でも固くない?
Yeah, just here.
うん、ちょっとここに
I got it.
取れた
取れたー
Wow, that's amazing.
えー、すげー
copper?
どう?
Amazing.
すごー
How about this shape?
この形はどう?
Yeah, nice.
うん、いいね
I wish it were a little bigger.
もうちょっとおっきいのがいいけど
Would you like something a little bigger?
もうちょっとおっきいのがいい?
Because it's big.
おっきいから
Yeah.
うん
It's pretty big, though.
結構おっきいよね、でも
Yeah.
うん
Because Rin-chan has a small face.
だってりんちゃん顔ちっちゃいからさ、
Look.
ほら
No, it's not that small.
いや、ここまではちっちゃくないよ
Isn't it so small?
ここまでちっちゃくない?
Yeah.
うん
Big, big.
おっきいの、おっきいの
Which one is the big one?
おっきいのどれだ?
this is?
これは?
I got this.
これ、ね、もった
Ah, I cut it.
あー、切っちゃった
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
It's a little difficult to cut.
ちょっと切るのが難しい
Cut?
切る?
Oh, here it goes.
お、いけた
oh.
おー
Oh, that's amazing.
おー、すごい
That's amazing.
すごいね
nice.
いいね
It feels really good, really.
いい感じ、めっちゃ
Ah, this is good.
あ、これいいじゃん
Isn't it big?
おっきくない?
It's definitely big.
たしかにおっきい
Because I want to eat a lot.
いっぱい食べたいから
Do you want to eat a lot?
いっぱい食べたいの?
Yeah.
うん
Did you eat dinner today?
今日ご飯食べた?
I haven't eaten today yet.
今日ご飯ね、まだ食べてないんだ
Haven't you eaten?
食べてないんだ?
not at all?
全然?
Yeah.
うん
Ah, I see.
あ、そっか
Wow, there are insects.
うわ、虫いる
Wow, wow.
うわ、やば
String.
ひも
Oh no.
やば
picture?
え?
What can I do?
どうしないな
Pokopoko right?
ポコポコでしょ?
Sorry.
ごめんな
I'm not good with insects.
俺、虫苦手なんだもん
picture?
え?
insect?
虫?
I'm really bad at it.
マジで苦手なの
Region, there's a bug behind you.
リジョン、後ろに虫ついてるよ
Really?
本当に?
Take it.
取ってよ
Eh, why why?
え、なんでなんで?
Take it.
取ってね
取ってよ
This is really bad.
マジやばい
Take it.
取ってよ
What is this?
なにこれ?
Light insect.
点灯虫
I really am.
本当にいるよ
Take it.
取ってよ
picture?
え?
Where?
どこで?
Pokopoko right?
ポコポコでしょ?
You can take it, right?
取れるでしょ?
Wow.
うっそー
Sorry.
ごめんね
I wanted to surprise you.
びっくりさせたかったな
Don't startle me.
びっくりさせないでよ
Oh, that?
あ、それ?
Region, I'm sorry.
リジョン、ごめん
Really.
本当にさ
what?
なに?
This time I'm serious.
今度はマジでいる
what?
なに?
insect.
虫
Hey, take it.
ねえ、取ってよ
picture?
え?
Take it.
取って
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
Take it.
取 って
Really.
本当に
Really please.
本当にお願い
help me.
助けて
Really.
本当に
Really take it.
本当に取って
Wait a minute.
ちょっと 待って ね
Ah, yeah.
あ、うん
Did you get it?
取れた?
Take it.
取れて
thank you.
ありがとう
I'm really surprised now.
マジびっくりした、今
You can touch it.
触れるじゃん
No, I touched it, but it was a very small insect.
いや、触れるんだけど、めっちゃ小さい虫だったの
I see.
なるほどね
Large insects were impossible.
大きい虫が無理だった
A big insect.
大きい虫が
Large insects were impossible.
大きい虫が無理だった
Are the insects okay?
虫自体は平気?
As long as I see it.
見る分には
It would be really impossible if it followed me.
自分に付いてたら本当に無理
Well, I see.
まあ、そっか
That's right.
そうだよね
Wait, aren't there any of these?
てか、こっち一個もなくない?
There's nothing here.
こっちなんもない
Shall we go somewhere else soon?
そろそろ違うとこ行く?
Please, stay with me until the end.
お願い、最後まで付き合って
Until the end?
最後まで?
No?
ダ メ?
Okay.
いいよ
TRUE?
本当?
Okay.
いいよ
Okay, okay.
いいよ、いいよ
Well then, why don't you just take a little more?
じゃあ、あともうちょっと取ったらいいんでしようか
Moreover, I got quite a lot of it.
しかも、結構取れたから
Yeah, I took a lot of big ones.
うん、大きいのいっぱい取った
You took it.
取ったね
How many grams?
何グラムかな?
何グラムでしょう
How many grams?
何グラムだ?
400?
400 how many grams?
400何グラム?
How much?
どのくらい?
What is that?
それ何?
Didn't you say it was just 400?
それ、ギリ400言ってない?
I'm telling you.
言ってるよ
That's a lie.
嘘だ
Really.
本当に
Seriously?
マジで?
405?
Well then, it's 405.
じゃあ、405だね
Where can I pay for this?
これ、どこでお会計するんだろう?
Is it over there?
あっちかな?
this.
この
Let's go outside for once, then.
一回外でよっか、じゃあ
It's this way.
こっちだね
Yes, Rin-chan, this is it.
はい、りんちゃん、これ
Yeah, thank you.
うん、ありがとう
It was never this big.
なんかこんな、 おっきいのなかったね
No, probably, all the really big mushrooms were taken away.
いや、多分ね、めちゃくちゃでかいキノコは全部取られちゃってた
That's right.
んだ よね
そうだよね
I wish it were okay, since it's here in the mountains.
なんかもしよかったらさ、この辺山だから、
The two of us go looking for some big mushrooms.
なんか二人で、おっきいキノコでも探しに行く
Eh, let's go, let's go?
え、行こう行こう?
Yeah.
うん
But is there?
でも、ある?
On a normal mountain.
普通の山に
No, I think there is.
いや、あると思う
natural mushrooms.
天然キノコ
Can I eat it?
食べれるの?
that.
それ
You can eat it, right?
食べれるでしょ
On the other hand, if we both look into it, we'll see.
逆に、それを二人で調べて、 ほら、
I just received the instructions and how to bake.
今、説明書とかさ、焼き方とかもらったから、
It's true.
ほ んとだ
Let's check that out and then go eat.
それ調べて、あと食べに行こうよ、
Well then.
じゃあ
Let's go eat, let's go get it.
食べに行こうじゃない、取りに行こう
Yeah, okay.
うん、いいよ
How to bake this, can I do it when I get home?
これで焼き方、家帰ったらできる?
hey.
ね
Do you want your mom to do it for you?
お母さんにやってもらう?
Maybe I should ask my mom to do it for me.
お母さんにやってもらおうかな
You can eat this all the way to the stem.
これ、 軸まで食べれるんだ、これ
which one?
どれ?
This mushroom.
このキノコ
Oh, can you eat all of this?
あ、これ全部食べれるの?
Yeah.
うん
If you cut just the bottom part,
この下のギリギリのところだけ切ったら、
Looks like I can eat it.
食べれるみたい
Seriously?
マジで?
But I'm not good at this.
でも、これ下手とんない
Normally I would take it, but...
普通は取るよね、でもね
Take, take.
取る取る
I'll take it.
取るよね
Yeah, I'll cut the shaft.
うん、軸切っちゃう
Does Rin-chan cook?
りんちゃんって料理するの?
I will!
するよ!
picture?
え?
I will!
するよ!
Seriously?
マジで?
Do it.
するする
What about studying?
勉強は?
Recently.
最近は
I'll study.
勉強はするよ
Because mom is busy with work.
ママが仕事忙しいから
Oh, is that so?
あ、そうなの?
I see.
なるほどね
That's amazing.
すごいなぁ
すごいよね
Is it this way?
こっちかな?
Yeah, this way.
うん、こっち
Okay.
よ いしょ
Rin-chan.
りんちゃん
Yeah?
うん?
This is it.
これさ
Yeah.
うん
What's going on?
どうなってんの?
It's here.
ここなんだよね
Ah, that's cute.
あ、かわいい
Lay it down.
横にして
It's big.
おっきいよね
I'm creating it.
つくりくりしてる
The first one.
先のツ
Look here.
こ っち見て
Look.
ほら
Look down.
下を向き出して
Oh, that's terrible.
あーやばい
So cute.
めっちゃかわいい
It's so erotic.
めっちゃエロいね
So, did you see this?
じゃ、こっち見た?
Very low.
めちゃめちゃ下とか
Oh bitch.
あービッチ
Looks like Karin.
カリンのようだね
Being licked from below.
下から舐められて
I'm so sorry.
めっちゃすみません
Just go to your head.
ちょっと頭に行けよ
A little bit
ちょっちょっ
Hey, hey.
ちょ っちょっ
Tighten the tooth canal under this spot ground.
このスポットグラウンド下の歯道締めっけ
Excuse me for a moment.
ちょっとすみません
a little bit?
ちょっと?
Okay?
いいか?
I can't help but feel like Rin-chan.
そんなにりんちゃんに身がなっちゃう
I don't notice.
気がつかない
It's amazing.
すんごいビラビラ
Rin-chan's Chris game is beautiful.
りんちゃんのクリスゲーきれい
Because I'm getting really horny.
めっちゃムラムラしてきたから
Can I drink it?
飲みちゃっていい?
Did you drink?
飲んだの?
Okay?
いいか?
Did you just use your finger?
今指でいった?
Did you go to a Chris game?
クリスゲーでいった?
Which one?
どっちの?
Both.
どっちも
Rin-chan, I've been here twice now.
りんちゃんさ、 今2回もいったから
He said it was mine again.
また俺の方にあるって言ってた
That face is so erotic.
その顔めちゃくちゃエロい
It's so cute.
めちゃくちゃかわいい
Messed up
めちゃくちゃ
horse
う ま
stomach.
い
It's insanely delicious.
め ちゃくちゃうまい
Don't ask Rin-chan.
り んちゃん頼むなって
I'm so sorry.
めっちゃすみません
Na
な
To?
に?
Did you say your shoulders are like this?
こんな 肩申った?
Yeah.
うん
You ate that much.
そんなに食べたじゃん
Four years ago.
4つ前になって
Will I be able to have a baby?
赤ちゃんできちゃうの?
I can have a baby.
赤ちゃんできちゃうの
Because they don't really get chewed out.
本当にチューなんてされないから
Since middle school?
中学校以来?
中 学校以来?
That's fine.
いいじゃん
hand?
手?
why?
なんで?
Even your hands are cute.
手でもかわいいな
It feels really nice to the touch.
すっごい触り心地いい
Is that so?
そうかな?
It feels just right.
ちょうどいい感じだね
You look sweet.
甘やかそうな顔してる
From the body as it is.
そのまま体からして
Don't do it without licking the bottom.
下舐めずにしないで
I'm licking the bottom.
下ペロペロしてる
Don't look at me.
こっち見ないで
It's so erotic.
す っごいエロい
The bottom is amazing.
その下すっごい
And it paid off.
そして元付きましたね
It feels really, really good.
めっちゃめっちゃいい感じだね
Baby here.
赤ちゃんのここ
Certainly well.
確かによく
It's slippery.
ズルズルやん